Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/gilsheinfeld (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Product Management
Product Development
Software Development

Patents

Route monitoring in a network management system

Method of improving user interaction with an object management tool

Generating synthetic advertisements for an electronic environment

CONNECTIVITY OUTAGE
DETECTION: NETWORK/IP SLA
PROBES REPORTING BUSINESS
IMPACT INFORMATION

Route monitoring in a network management system

Gil Sheinfeld

CTO at Fiverr. I am hiring.

Israel

Summary

Business, Product, and Technology Executive with extensive experience in multiple disciplines including e-commerce, large scale web, social, and ad tech. Successful track record of building and leading product and technology organizations, developing amazing products and platforms. Deep understanding of the business and the user experience. Specializes in leading product vision and innovation, executing ambitious business programs and leading advanced solutions that set product and technical foundations for long-term revenue growth. Worked for both small companies and large companies. Performed technical due diligence for companies in multiple domains, resulting in multiple acquisitions totaling more than \$500M. I was part of executive team selling Amobee for \$321M, and part of the executive team taking Fiverr to an IPO.

Experience

Fiverr

CTO

January 2017 - Present (4 years 7 months)

Tel Aviv Area, Israel

Fiverr is a global marketplace that connects freelancers and businesses for digital services. I lead the Product and Technology organization.

We continue our rapid growth, come join us!

Beach Bum Ltd.

CEO

November 2015 - June 2016 (8 months)

Tel Aviv

Beach Bum is an interactive games company founded in 2015 by leading industry veterans. I helped the founders with the launch of their first game.

Tango Me Chief Monetization Officer

May 2015 - October 2015 (6 months)

Mountain View, California

Led the monetization of Tango Me. With more than 300 million downloads, Tango is one of the leading social messaging applications. During my tenure, I drove the vision and monetization strategy, creating partnerships as well as designing and building platforms and processes for growing Tango's current and long-term monetization.

Amobee

4 years 2 months

CTO

July 2013 - April 2015 (1 year 10 months)

Amobee offers marketers, agencies, publishers and operators the most advanced cross channel digital marketing technology platform and solutions with powerful AI at its core.

- Led Amobee product strategy, vision, and roadmap
- Led Amobee technical vision and roadmap
- Managed the global product, engineering, and tech operation teams (staff of 200 technologists) that build platforms which support a business worth hundreds of millions of dollars
- Expanded beyond mobile to cross-channel, marketing insights, social marketing, and more
- Drove technology evaluation for M&A and strategic deals
- Was the local GM for the Israeli office

SVP Worldwide Product and Engineering May 2012 - June 2013 (1 year 2 months)

- Led the expansion of Amobee line of products to multiple products:
- Amobee Mobile RTB Exchange
- Amobee Mobile Conversion Tracking RTB DSP

- Amobee 3D an advanced immersive rich media technology
- Grew the product and technical global teams
- · Acquired Adjitsu

VP Engineering

March 2011 - April 2012 (1 year 2 months)

- Led the Product, Tech strategy and diligence leading to selling Amobee to Singtel for \$321M
- Enhanced the Amobee Ad Server and SSP to become RTB Exchange and SaaS for Publishers, creating new business for Amobee
- Built Conversion Tracking DSP to support the Cost Per Install business

A9.com (Amazon.com)

Director of Engineering

November 2007 - January 2011 (3 years 3 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

- A9.com powers advanced online advertising programs for some of the world's largest websites, including Amazon.com and other prime online properties.
- Grew attributed revenue 5x during my tenure.
- Led the architecture and development of Amazon.com Ad Platforms.
- Directed senior group of engineers, scientists and product managers, in a very dynamic environment.
- Managed teams handling the design and development for several online advertising programs - Display Ads, Ad Exchange, Product Ads, Clickriver Ads and Sponsored Links.
- Successfully built the first generation of systems that support multiple new business initiatives with comprehensive functionality and on a tight schedule.

Cisco

9 years 4 months

Senior Manager, Software Development September 2006 - October 2007 (1 year 2 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

- Led 250+ team members (in India and US) on multi-year, global ANA 4.0 product releases.
- Manages 60 matrixed reports who build/develop converged management platform releases.
- Selected/managed technologies, tasks, schedules and operational activities to meet very aggressive deadlines.

Manager, Software Development January 2002 - August 2006 (4 years 8 months)

Manager / Software Development – Routing & Switching Group (7/2004 – 8/2006)

Manager / Software Development – Cisco Access Control Server (8/2003 – 6/2004)

Manager / Software Development – QoS & SLA Management Applications (1/2002 – 7/2003)

Software Engineer
July 1998 - December 2001 (3 years 6 months)
Tel Aviv

Kulmos Technologies Itd Software Developer March 1996 - December 1997 (1 year 10 months)

Education

Tel Aviv University
M.B.A., Information Technology · (1999 - 2001)

Tel Aviv University
BSc, Computer Science · (1996 - 1998)

Tel Aviv University
BSc, Statistics and Operations Research · (1996 - 1998)